// creating an array and passing the number, questions, options, and answers
let questions = [
   {
    numb: 1,
    question: "What does the “https://” at the beginning of a URL denote, as opposed to “http://” (without the “s”)?",
    answer: "B. That information entered into the site is encrypted" ,
    options: [
      "A. That the site has special high definition",
      "B. That information entered into the site is encrypted"
      ,"C. That the site is the newest version available",
      "D. That the site is not accessible to certain computers"
    ]
  }, 
  {
    numb: 2,
    question: "Which of the following is an example of a “phishing” attack?",
    answer: "D. All of the above",
    options: [
      "A. Sending someone an email that contains a malicious link that is disguised to look like an email from someone the person knows",
      "B. Creating a fake website that looks nearly identical to a real website in order to trick users into entering their login information",
      "C. Sending someone a text message that contains a malicious link that is disguised to look like a notification that the person has won a contest",
      "D. All of the above"
    ]
  }, 
  {
    numb: 3,
    question: " Which of the following four passwords is the most secure?",
    answer: "B. WTh!5Z",
    options: [
      "A. Boat123",
      "B. WTh!5Z",
      "C. into*48",
      "D. 123456"
    ]
  }, 
  {
    numb: 4,
    question: "Criminals access someones computer and encrypt the users personal files and data. The user is unable to access this data unless they pay the criminals to decrypt the files. This practice is called?",
    answer: "D. Ransomware",
    options: [
      "A. Botnet",
      "B. Spam",
      "C. Driving",
      "D. Ransomware"
    ]
  },
   {
    numb: 5,
    question: "What kind of cybersecurity risks can be minimized by using a Virtual Private Network (VPN)?",
    answer: "A. Use of insecure Wi-Fi networks",
    options: [
      "A. Use of insecure Wi-Fi networks",
      "B. Keylogging",
      "C. De-anonymization by network operators",
      "D. Phishing attacks"
    ]
  }, 
   {
    numb: 6,
    question: "You have a hard copy of a design document that you want to dispose of. What would you do?",
    answer: "B. Shred it using a shredder",
    options: [
      "A. Throw it in any dustbin",
      "B. Shred it using a shredder",
      "C. Give it to the office boy to reuse it for other purposes",
      "D. Be environment friendly and reuse it for writing"
    ]
  }, 
   {
    numb: 7,
    question: "When is the best time to lie to your information security auditor or officer?",
    answer: "D. None of the above",
    options: [
      "A. If you want to cover up your best friend’s faults or mistakes",
      "B. If the security auditor is not your friend and cannot be trusted",
      "C. If it impacts the termination of the key people in your organization",
      "D. None of the above"
    ]
  }, 
   {
    numb: 8,
    question: "Cyber criminals only target large companies. True or False?",
    answer: "False",
    options: [
      "True",
      "False",
      "",
      ""
    ]
  }, 
   {
    numb: 9,
    question: "An email from your boss asks for the name, addresses, and credit card information of the company’s top clients. The email says it’s urgent and to please reply right away. You should reply right away. True or False?",
    answer: "False",
    options: [
      "True",
      "False",
      "",
      ""
    ]
  }, 
   {
    numb: 10,
    question: "If a public Wi-Fi network (such as in an airport or café) requires a password to access, is it generally safe to use that network for sensitive activities such as online banking?",
    answer: "B. No, it is not safe",
    options: [
      "A. Yes, it is safe" ,
      "B. No, it is not safe" ,
      "",
      ""
    ]
  }
 
];